https://doula.org.uk/privacy-and-cookies-policy/

MenuHomeAbout Doula UKAbout Doula UKHistoryDirectors of Doula UK CICLeadership TeamVolunteer Opportunities with Doula UKBecome a Friend of Doula UKThe Doula MagazinePressPolicy Documents CloseInformation for familiesFind a DoulaFind A DoulaAbout doulasEvidence in support of doulasDoula Services Gift VoucherFurther Information for familesThird Party Doula support orgsAntenatal Workshop for Parents CloseBecoming a doulaTrainingDoula UK Introductory WorkshopBursary Places available – Doula UK Introductory WorkshopList of Doula UK Approved CoursesUseful ResourcesJoin Doula UKBecoming a doulaJoin Doula UKDoula UK Mentoring and Recognition CloseSupport Doula UKAccess FundDoula Access FundApply to the Access FundDonate to the Access Fund CloseNewsMembersContact Us
This privacy policy sets out how “Doula UK CIC” uses and protects any information that you give “Doula UK CIC” when you use this website.
“Doula UK CIC” is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
“Doula UK CIC” may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy was updated on 4th June 2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping
We may use the information to improve our products and services
We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We also use cookies to monitor the logins of users who access the site using a password and also when a user purchases items from the website.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. No cookies are set by other companies or organisations other than Google (for our analytics purposes) and social networking sites may also monitor access if you interact with the site (eg using a Facebook like button).
Most web browsers automatically  accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@doula.org.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you, for free, under the Data Protection Act 2018 and the General Data Protection Act 2018.
If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact:
Syanne Walker -Data Protection Officer dataprotection@doula.org.uk
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Shopping Basket
Support our work
By joining as a Friend of Doula UK:
Join NOW
By shopping:
Shop at Amazon
By donating directly to the Access Fund:
Doula UK is open.
Doulas are offering in person and virtual support at this time and doula training is available.
×
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
